Guide to the Richard Brown Baker Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- March 2004 Acquisition, 1959-2004; 2; (2 boxes)
  - Artist Files
    - Samplers from Baker's diary as he developed as a collector from 1952-1960, copy, 1987 (Box 78)
    - Ackroyd - Anderson, undated (Box 78)
    - Adams, Robert, 1964-1991 (Box 78)
    - Bartow, Rick, 1989-1991 (Box 78)
    - Baxter - Brown - Caro - Capogrossi, 1960-1990 (Box 78)
    - Belleny, John, 1982-1990 (Box 78)
    - Blake, Peter, 1968-1981 (Box 78)
    - Boshier, Peter, 1983-1987 (Box 78)
    - Buckley, Peter, 1951-1986 (Box 78)
    - Card, Greg, 1970-1981 (Box 78)
    - Carter - Chadwick, 1966-1991 (Box 78)
    - Cornielle - Cuertas, 1962-1992 (Box 78)
    - Davies - Evans, 1967-1989 (Box 78)
    - Farber-Gourfain, 1960-1990 (Box 78)
    - Green, Anthony, 1979-1987 (Box 78)
    - Gregor, Harold, 1989-1991 (Box 78)
    - Hacklin - Hidai, 1946-1992 (Box 78)
    - Hilton, Roger, 1959-1966 (Box 78)
    - Hockney, David, 1968-1991; 5 (Box 79)
    - Hodgkin, Howard, 1981-1989 (Box 79)
    - Hollweg - Hutchinson, 1966-1988 (Box 79)
    - Jacklin - Kootz, 1960-1979 (Box 79)
    - Lamis - Louden, 1961-1985 (Box 79)
    - Mason - Mitchel, 1985-1992 (Box 79)
    - Mock - Mor, 1957-1990 (Box 79)
    - Moore, Henry, 1979-1986 (Box 79)
    - Nadler - Passmore, 1967-1989 (Box 79)
    - Nicholson, Ben, 1969-1991 (Box 79)
- December 2006 Acquisition, 1941-2004; 3; 7; (7 boxes)
  Formerly Uncat MSS 917.
  - Artist Files
    - Art List, compiled by Yale University Art Gallery, 2004 March 29 (Box 80)
    - Afro, Max Beckman, 1958-1990 (Box 80)
    - Agosti, Jean Paul, 1958-1990 (Box 80)
    - Albers, John, 1983-1987 (Box 80)
    - Albers, Josef, 1958-1984; 4 (Box 80)
    - Aldera - Altman, 1958-1992 (Box 80)
    - Andre, Carl, 1966-1992 (Box 80)
    - Andrejevic, Millet, 1963-1992 (Box 80)
    - Amenoff - Amighetti, 1986-1991 (Box 80)
    - Andrews, 1969-1981; 2 (Box 80)
    - Angell - Antes, 1969-1982 (Box 80)
    - Anuzkiewicz, 1965-1973 (Box 80)
    - Anthony, Carol, 1978-1991 (Box 80)
    - Antreasian - Arakawa, 1967-1978 (Box 80)
    - Arneson, Robert, 1975-1994; 3 (Box 80)
    - Arnoldi, Charles, 1987-1992 (Box 81)
    - Artswager, Richard, 1980-1992 (Box 81)
    - Arthur, Bradley, 1980-1994 (Box 81)
    - Assael, Steven, 1990-1994 (Box 81)
    - Avedisian, Edward, 1961-1975 (Box 81)
    - Azaceta, Luis Cruz, 1981-1994 (Box 81)
    - Baeder, John, 1979-1987 (Box 81)
    - Bannard, Walter Darby, 1968-1977; 2 (Box 81)
    - Baizerman - Baker, 1969-1995 (Box 81)
    - Baldessari, John, 1990-1995 (Box 81)
    - Barbeau, Marcel, 1964-1965 (Box 81)
    - Barnes, Robert, 1965-1985 (Box 81)
    - Barrett, Bill, 1989-1994 (Box 81)
    - Baruchello, GianFranco, 1966 (Box 81)
    - Baschet, Francois and Bernard, 1966-1980 (Box 81)
    - Basquiat, Jean-Michel, 1988-1992 (Box 81)
    - Bauermeister, Mary, 1967-1976 (Box 81)
    - Baynard, Ed, 1971-1976 (Box 81)
    - Baziotes, William, 1958-1983 (Box 81)
    - Beal, Jack, 1969-1985; 2 (Box 81)
    - Beauchamp, Robert, 1961-1983 (Box 82)
    - Bechtle, Robert, 1969-1984 (Box 82)
    - Beckman, William, 1982-1989 (Box 82)
    - Beltzig - Biederman, 1980-1987 (Box 82)
    - Bill - Bishop, 1963-1988 (Box 82)
    - Blackwell - Bohn, 1977-1990 (Box 82)
    - Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1959-1989; 3 (Box 82)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Boshier, Derek, 1986 (Box 82)
    - Bosman, Richard, 1983-1989 (Box 82)
    - Bouys, Jeanick, 1987 (Box 82)
    - Boxer, Stanley, 1972-1988 (Box 82)
    - Brach, Paul, 1968-1990 (Box 82)
    - Brainard, Joe, 1967-1975 (Box 82)
    - Briggs, Ernest, 1960-1991 (Box 82)
    - Broome, Michael, 1976 (Box 82)
    - Brody, Gandy, 1965-1983 (Box 82)
    - Brown, Frederick, 1985-1987 (Box 82)
    - Brown, Roger, 1973-1990 (Box 83)
    - Brown, William, 1962-1976 (Box 83)
    - Budd - Button, 1987-1989 (Box 83)
    - Burgo, Ignacio, 1997 (Box 83)
    - Burri, Alberto, 1963-1990 (Box 83)
    - Bury, Pol, 1966-1971 (Box 83)
    - Cady, Arthur, 1961-1989 (Box 83)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1961-1994; 4 (Box 83)
    - Callahan - Canogar, 1962-1990 (Box 83)
    - Capogrossi - Carles, 1976-1994 (Box 83)
    - Caro, Anthony, 1983-1994 (Box 83)
    - Carone - Carsman, 1962-1971 (Box 83)
    - Carter, Clarence, 1969 (Box 83)
    - Carton, Norman, 1958-1994; 3 (Box 83)
    - Castellini, Enrico, 1962-1987 (Box 83)
    - Cesar, Oliveira, 1985-1987 (Box 83)
    - Chaissac, Gaston, 1963-1988 (Box 83)
    - Chamberlain, John, 1959-1991; 4 (Box 83)
    - Chapman - Chase, 1980-1993 (Box 84)
    - Chevalier, Peter, 1983-1988 (Box 84)
    - Chai, Sandro, 1984-1988 (Box 84)
    - Childs, Bernard, 1959-1990 (Box 84)
    - Chillada, Eduardo, 1962-1987 (Box 84)
    - Chimes, Tom, 1965-1978 (Box 84)
    - Cicero, Carmen, 1959-1988 (Box 84)
    - Clark, Michael, 1974-1980 (Box 84)
    - Clarke, John Clem, 1969-1980 (Box 84)
    - Clawson, Rex, 1963-1964 (Box 84)
    - Clemente, Francesco, 1986-1990 (Box 84)
    - Clerk, Pierre, 1971-1973 (Box 84)
    - Clough, Charles, 1991 (Box 84)
    - Clutz, William, 1971-1988 (Box 84)
    - Close, Chuck, 1978-1991 (Box 84)
    - Coates, Ross, 1968, 1974 (Box 84)
    - Cohen, Harold, 1964-1987 (Box 84)
    - Cole, Alphaeus, 1983-1989 (Box 84)
    - Comer, Roy, 1967-1988 (Box 84)
    - Comtois, Louis, 1976-1988 (Box 84)
    - Condo, George, 1988-1994; 2 (Box 84)
    - Cone, Davis, 1982-1988 (Box 84)
    - Congdon, William, 1962-1968 (Box 84)
    - Conner, Bruce, 1967-1989; 2 (Box 84)
    - Corbett, Edward, 1955-1990 (Box 85)
    - Corpora, Anthony, 1959-1963 (Box 85)
    - Cottingham, Robert, 1970-1994 (Box 85)
    - Cousins, Harold, 1961-1972 (Box 85)
    - Cragg, Tony, 1962-1989 (Box 85)
    - Cronbach, Robert, 1991-1992 (Box 85)
    - Crimmins - Cross - Crowl, 1951-1981 (Box 85)
    - Crutchfield, William, 1977-1976 (Box 85)
    - Cuevas, Jose Luis, 1964-1989; 2 (Box 85)
    - Cuningham, Bruce, 1987-1992 (Box 85)
    - Currie, Ken, 1983-1993 (Box 85)
    - D'Arcangelo, Allan, 1969-1990 (Box 85)
    - Daphnis, Nassos, 1963-1990 (Box 85)
    - D'Arista, Robert, 1956-1967 (Box 85)
    - David, Michael, 1989-1991 (Box 85)
    - Davie, Allan, 1958-1985 (Box 85)
    - Davila, Carlos, 1969-1975 (Box 85)
    - Davis, Lee Baxter, 1973-1975 (Box 85)
    - Davis, Gene, 1968-1973 (Box 85)
    - Davis, Ron, 1964-1989 (Box 85)
    - DeAndrea, John De, 1987-1991 (Box 85)
    - DeForest, Roy, 1963-1994 (Box 85)
    - Dehn, Adolf, 1941-1972 (Box 85)
    - De Kooning, Willem, 1960-1990; 4 (Box 85)
    - De Knight, Avel de, 1980-1995 (Box 86)
    - Delavante, Sydney, 1959-1976 (Box 86)
    - DeLap, Tony, 1965-1982 (Box 86)
    - Del Grosso, James, 1989, 1992 (Box 86)
    - De Niro, Robert, 1958-1990 (Box 86)
    - Dewey, David, 1989-1990 (Box 86)
    - Dickson, Jane, 1987-1992 (Box 86)
    - Di Donna, Porfirio, 1978-1988 (Box 86)
    - Diebenkorn, Richard, 1964-1995; 4 (Box 86)
    - Dill, Lesley, 1971-1994; 2 (Box 86)
    - Diller, Bungoyne, 1961-1990; 3 (Box 86)
    - Dine, Jim, 1962-1996; 4 (Box 86)
- June 2007 Acquisition, 1953-2002; 4; 20; (20 boxes)
  Formerly Uncat MSS 955.
  - Artist Files
    - Di Suivero, Marc, 1966-1980; 2 (Box 87)
    - Donati, Enrico, 1955-1981 (Box 87)
    - Dorazio, Pierro, 1966-1981 (Box 87)
    - Downes, Rackstraw, 1975-1992 (Box 87)
    - Doyle - Drake - Drapell, 1978-1989 (Box 87)
    - Drisch, Russell, 1975-1988 (Box 87)
    - Dubuffet, Jean, 1960-1988; 6 (Box 87)
      Includes Pace museum Dubuffet puzzle
    - Dudley, Randy, 1979-1988 (Box 87)
    - Dufy, Raoul, 1968-1991 (Box 87)
    - Dumont - Dunkan - Eddy, 1964-1976 (Box 87)
    - Eilshemius - Elozua, 1959-1982 (Box 87)
    - Ellenburg - Elkins - Embry, 1965-1988 (Box 87)
    - Estes, Richard, 1976-1994 (Box 87)
    - Evans, Donald, 1975-1991 (Box 87)
    - Fahlstrom, Oyvind, 1966-1987 (Box 87)
    - Fangor - Fares, 1969-1976 (Box 87)
    - Feely, Paul, 1966-1992 (Box 88)
    - Feininger, Lyonel, 1936-1991 (Box 88)
    - Feito, Luis, 1960-1963 (Box 88)
    - Ferber, Herbert, 1969-1985 (Box 88)
    - Ferguson, Max, 1986-1990 (Box 88)
    - Ferren, John, 1954-1987 (Box 88)
    - Fischer - Fischl, 1964-1988 (Box 88)
    - Fish, Janet, 1976-1990 (Box 88)
    - Folchi - Flood - Folon, 1973-1994 (Box 88)
    - Foulks - Foon, 1964-1992 (Box 88)
    - Francisco - Frank, 1974-1987 (Box 88)
    - Francis, Sam, 1966-1994; 2 (Box 88)
    - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1965-1987; 2 (Box 88)
    - Freckelton - Fulton, 1966-1986 (Box 88)
    - Fussmann - Gates, 1976-1986 (Box 88)
    - Gauguin - German, 1973-1994 (Box 88)
    - Gibbons, Arthur, 1982-1991 (Box 88)
    - Gingerich, Glasco, 1961-1986 (Box 89)
    - Goings, Ralph, 1976-1994; 2 (Box 89)
    - Goldring - Goodman, 1959-1981 (Box 89)
    - Goodnough, Robert, 1957-1992; 2 (Box 89)
    - Goodwin, Guy, 1987-1989 (Box 89)
    - Gordy - Gottlieb, 1977-1990 (Box 89)
    - Gray - Green, 1977-1986 (Box 89)
    - Grenon - Grooms, 1976-1985 (Box 89)
    - Groth, Jan, 1976-1992 (Box 89)
    - Guerrero, Jose, 1962-1987 (Box 89)
    - Gundelfinger, John, 1974-1991 (Box 89)
    - Haacke, Hans, 1969-1992 (Box 89)
    - Haas, Richard, 1977-1990 (Box 89)
    - Hall - Hamilton, 1975-1991 (Box 89)
    - Han, H.N., 1967-1979 (Box 89)
    - Hanson, Duane, 1978-1994; 2 (Box 89)
    - Hanson, Duane, 1978-1994; 3 (Box 90)
    - Harding - Hart, 1975-1984 (Box 90)
    - Hartigan, Grace, 1962-1966 (Box 90)
    - Hartung, Hans, 1957-1979 (Box 90)
    - Harvey, James, 1953-1962 (Box 90)
    - Hatchet, Duayne, 1969-1984 (Box 90)
    - Heinze, Gus, 1992 (Box 90)
    - Heinzen, Elga, 1990 (Box 90)
    - Heinzer, Michael, 1973-1988 (Box 90)
    - Helander, Bruce, 1979-1994 (Box 90)
    - Held, Al, 1960-1991; 2 (Box 90)
    - Herbin, Auguste, 1964-1969 (Box 90)
    - Herfield, Phyllis, 1991 (Box 90)
    - Hill, Clinton, 1969-1987 (Box 90)
    - Hodgkin, Howard, 1987 (Box 90)
    - Hoffman, Eric, 1971-1982 (Box 90)
    - Hoffman, Martin, 1975-1981 (Box 90)
    - Hofmann, Hans, 1955-1991; 3 (Box 90)
    - Holland, Tom, 1969-1992 (Box 90)
    - Hollowell, David, 1991-1992 (Box 91)
    - Honegger, Gottfried, 1956-1970 (Box 91)
    - Hosiasson, Philippe, 1956-1962 (Box 91)
    - House - Houston - Huddleton, 1965-1991 (Box 91)
    - Hudson, Andrew, 1982-1983 (Box 91)
    - Hudson, Robert, 1990 (Box 91)
      Includes photograph of Robert Brown Baker standing beside Hudson's sculpture.
    - Hull, John, 1989 (Box 91)
    - Humphrey, David, 1989-1991 (Box 91)
    - Humphrey, Richard, undated (Box 91)
    - Hunt,Richard, 1975-1985; 2 (Box 91)
    - Imanka, Kumiko, 1965 (Box 91)
    - Indiana, Robert, 1962-1981; 2 (Box 91)
    - Immendorf - Ipousteguy - Israel, 1984-1994 (Box 91)
    - Ippoleto, Angelo, 1958-1984 (Box 91)
    - Jansons - Jessup, 1978-1989 (Box 91)
    - Johnson, Martin, 1981 (Box 91)
    - Jacquette, Yvonne, 1974-1992 (Box 91)
    - Jaudon, Valerie, 1984-1990 (Box 91)
    - Jenkins, Paul, 1963-1989 (Box 91)
    - Jimenez, Luis, 1974-1992; 2 (Box 91)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1970-1990; 6 (Box 91)
    - Jones, Allen, 1964-1985 (Box 92)
    - Johnson, Guy, 1962-1994 (Box 92)
    - Johnson, Lester, 1964-1988; 2 (Box 92)
    - Judd, Donald, 1967-1994; 2 (Box 92)
    - Jaszczyk, James, 1976-1980 (Box 92)
    - Kahn, Wolf, 1969-1989; 2 (Box 92)
    - Kane - Kapner, 1964, 1988 (Box 92)
    - Kent, William, 1963-1964 (Box 92)
    - Kelly, Jay, 1989 (Box 92)
    - Kessler, Alan, 1980-1989 (Box 92)
    - Kantor, Morris, 1959-1982 (Box 92)
    - Kantor, Tadeusz, 1960, 1990 (Box 92)
    - Katzen, Lila, 1979-1988 (Box 92)
    - Katzman, Herbert, 1957-1978 (Box 92)
    - Kearl, Stanley, 1963-1985 (Box 92)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1968-1990; 2 (Box 92)
    - Kelly, Tim, 1983 (Box 92)
    - Kendrick, Mel, 1974-191 (Box 92)
    - Khanna, Krishen, 1964-1983 (Box 92)
    - Kiefer, Anselm, 1985-1990 (Box 92)
    - Kieveitt, Joseph, 1982 (Box 92)
    - Kim - King - Knaupp - Kolibal, 1966-1989 (Box 92)
    - Kitaj, R.B., 1966-1981 (Box 92)
    - Klasen, Peter, 1960-1969 (Box 92)
    - Klenk, William, 1963-1980 (Box 92)
    - Kline, Franz, 1959-1990; 6 (Box 93)
    - Koenigstein, W., 1983-1985 (Box 93)
    - Kolin, Sacha, 1969-1972 (Box 93)
    - Komodore, Bill, 1975-1978 (Box 93)
    - Kosciansky, Leonard, 1983-1995 (Box 93)
    - Krauss, Anthony, 1968-1989 (Box 93)
    - Kruschenick, Nicholas, 1964-1990 (Box 93)
    - Kuno, Shin, 1974 (Box 93)
    - Kuchenmeister, Rainer, 1971-1973 (Box 93)
    - Kricke, Norbert, 1968, 1988 (Box 93)
    - Kurland, Bruce, 1974-1988 (Box 93)
    - Kushner, Robert, 1985-1993 (Box 93)
    - Kuwayama, Tadaaki, 1963-1992 (Box 93)
    - Lam - Lanceley - La Fontaine - Levinston - Levitan - Lewitin (Box 93)
    - Langlais, Bernard, 1958-1986 (Box 93)
    - Lausen, Uwe, 1966 (Box 93)
    - Lazzari, Pietro, 1958-1976 (Box 93)
    - Le Brun, Christopher, 1990 (Box 93)
    - Lee, David, 1962-1977 (Box 93)
    - Leslie, Alfred, 1959-1992 (Box 93)
    - Le Va, Barry, 1973-1990 (Box 93)
    - Levee, John, 1957-1969 (Box 93)
    - Levi, Josef, 1967-1990 (Box 93)
    - Levine, Jack, 1945-1991 (Box 94)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1958-1992 (Box 94)
    - Libermann, Alexander, 1974-1988 (Box 94)
    - Liebman, Gerhardt, 1976, 1979 (Box 94)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1960-199?; 9 (Box 94)
    - Lindner, Richard, 1964-1971 (Box 94)
    - Lipski, Donald, 1975-1990 (Box 94)
    - Lobdell, Frank, 1963-1987 (Box 94)
    - Lobello, Peter, 1980-1984 (Box 94)
    - Louis, Morris, 1962-1988 (Box 94)
    - Longo - Lorber - Loring, 1977-1992 (Box 95)
    - Lowe - Luginbuhl - Lupertz - Lybecker, 1967-1993 (Box 95)
    - Mac-Entyre - Mackenzie - Magner, 1962-1968 (Box 95)
    - Magritte, Rene, 1963-1992 (Box 95)
    - Mahaffey, Noel, 1972-1973 (Box 95)
    - Mallory, Ronald, 1968-1973 (Box 95)
    - Mancini, Donald, 1985-1992 (Box 95)
    - Mangold, Robert, 1979-1987; 2 (Box 95)
    - Mangold, Sylvia Plimack, 1976-1986 (Box 95)
    - Marca-Relli, Conrad, 1958-1985 (Box 95)
    - Marden, Brice, 1970-1994 (Box 95)
    - Marini, Marino, 1964-1988 (Box 95)
    - Marshall - Martin - Marx, 1979-1994 (Box 95)
    - Martin, Agnes, 1967-1981; 2 (Box 95)
    - Maryan, 1977-1985 (Box 95)
    - Matisse, Henri, 1982, 1984 (Box 95)
    - Matthieu, Georges, 1955-1986; 2 (Box 95)
    - Matta, Roberto, 1964-1991; 2 (Box 95)
    - Maxera, Oscar, 1981-1987 (Box 95)
    - Maza, Fernando, 1972, 1978 (Box 95)
    - McGee, William, 1959-1991 (Box 96)
    - Meneeley, Edward, 1965-1982 (Box 96)
    - Mentor, Will, 1987-1988 (Box 96)
    - Meisbov, Hugh, 1959-1988 (Box 96)
    - Mahase, Jiva Soma, 1975, 1978 (Box 96)
    - Midgette, Willard, 1972, 1974 (Box 96)
    - Mieczkowski - Millares - Miller, R. - Miller, S., 1963-1986 (Box 96)
    - Mills - Moers - Mogensen - Molinari, 1981-1991 (Box 96)
    - Monnier - Montanez - Monteith - Montreuil, 1980-1989 (Box 96)
    - Moore, John, 1973-1984 (Box 96)
    - Morlotti - Morrell - Morrissey - Moses, 1977-1994 (Box 96)
    - Morris, Robert, 1963-1995; 4 (Box 96)
    - Moskowitz, Robert, 1970-1994 (Box 96)
    - Motherwell, Robert, 1957-1990; 6 (Box 96)
    - Motonaga, Sadamasa, 1966 (Box 96)
    - Moy, Seong, 1956-1990 (Box 96)
    - Murray, Clark, 1966-1984 (Box 96)
    - Mutchnik, Mark, 1974-1991 (Box 96)
    - Nadler, Harry, 1972 (Box 96)
    - Narkiewicz, Paul, 1971-1977 (Box 96)
    - Muller, Jan, 1962-1993 (Box 96)
    - Neil, Joe, 1977-1984 (Box 97)
    - Neri, Giancarlo, 1987, 1988 (Box 97)
    - Nesbitt, Lowell, 1964-1986; 3 (Box 97)
    - Nevelson, Louise, 1957-1989; 3 (Box 97)
    - Nickel, Jim, 1995 (Box 97)
    - Noland, Kenneth, 1965-1990; 3 (Box 97)
    - Notkin - Novros - Nutt, 1976-1992 (Box 97)
    - Obering, Mary, 1965, 1994 (Box 97)
    - Ochikubo, Tetsuo, 1957-1965 (Box 97)
    - Okamotos - Okimotos, 1960-1973 (Box 97)
    - Okulick, John, 1981-1992 (Box 97)
    - Odenburg, Claes, 1973-1991; 2 (Box 97)
    - Olitski, Jules, 1965-1989 (Box 97)
    - Oliveira, Nathan, 1961-1990; 2 (Box 98)
    - Onasato, Toshinobu, 1966-1978 (Box 98)
    - Ortins, David, 1991-1995 (Box 98)
    - Ortman, George, 1960-1965 (Box 98)
    - Ossorio, Alfonso, 1984-1995 (Box 98)
    - Ostlin - Owen, 1963-1988 (Box 98)
    - Pace, Stephen, 1960-1987 (Box 98)
    - Paluzzi, Rinaldo, 1976 (Box 98)
    - Pappas, George, undate (Box 98)
    - Paker, Raymond, 1960-1990 (Box 98)
    - Parks - Parsons, 1976-1991 (Box 98)
    - Paschke, Ed, 1980-1993 (Box 98)
    - Pasilis, Felix, 1956-1965 (Box 98)
    - Patkin, Izhar, 1989-1994 (Box 98)
    - Patterson, Clayton, 1983-1988 (Box 98)
    - Pearlstein, Philip, 1961-1995 (Box 98)
    - Pearson, Henry, 1962-1986 (Box 98)
    - Penck, A.R., 1986-1992 (Box 98)
    - Perelli - Peterson, 1961-1977 (Box 98)
    - Pettet - Pfaff, 1969-1991 (Box 98)
    - Pfreim, Bernard, undated (Box 98)
    - Pollack, Jackson, 1955-1995; 6 (Box 99)
    - Porcarao - Posey, 1970-1994 (Box 99)
    - Poons, Larry, 1966-1994 (Box 99)
    - Priest, Margaret, 1975-1982 (Box 99)
    - Prentiss, Chuck, 1969 (Box 99)
    - Prina, Stephen, 1989-1994 (Box 99)
    - Proctor, Patrick, 1967-1981 (Box 99)
    - Pye, William, 1968-1970 (Box 99)
    - Rabell - Raetz - Raffael, 1973-1994 (Box 99)
    - Rainer, Arnult, 1985-1994 (Box 99)
    - Ramanauskas, Dalia, 1974-1979 (Box 99)
    - Ramaseder, Josef, 1989-1992 (Box 99)
    - Ramirez, Eduardo, 1956-1988 (Box 99)
    - Ramon, Benito, 1979 (Box 99)
    - Randell, Richard, 1966-1971 (Box 99)
    - Rankin, V.V., 1991 (Box 99)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1968-1987; 4 (Box 99)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1968-1987; 3 (Box 99)
    - Reiland, Lowell, 1991-1994 (Box 100)
    - Remenick - Remington - Reva, 1965-1981 (Box 100)
    - Reinhardt, Ad, 1961-1991; 2 (Box 100)
    - Reynolds, Alan, 1956-1967 (Box 100)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1959-1963 (Box 100)
    - Reginato, Peter, 1971-1989 (Box 100)
    - Reibeck, Earl, 1973-1974 (Box 100)
    - Reicheck, Jesse, 1966-1972 (Box 100)
    - Rice, Dan, 1966-1970 (Box 100)
    - Riley, Bridget, 1966-1991 (Box 100)
    - Robbin, Tony, 1976-1988 (Box 100)
    - Robbins, Michael, 1978-1984 (Box 100)
    - Roche, Arnaldo, 1991 (Box 100)
    - Rockburne, Dorothea, 1978-1994 (Box 100)
    - Ronald, William, 1965-1972; 2 (Box 100)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1991; 2 (Box 100)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1964-1991; 5 (Box 101)
    - Roseman - Ross, 1968-1987 (Box 101)
    - Rosenthal, Tony, 1968-1987 (Box 101)
    - Roth, David, 1962-1972 (Box 101)
    - Roth, Tony, 1959-1975 (Box 101)
    - Rothko, Mark, 1974 (Box 101)
    - Roualt, Georges, 1949, 1963 (Box 101)
    - Rubin, Irwin, 1960-1962 (Box 101)
    - Rubin, Reuben, 1967 (Box 101)
    - Ruggeri, Pietro, 1962 (Box 101)
    - Ruscha, Edward, 1972-1998; 2 (Box 101)
    - Ryohei, Tanaka, 1974 (Box 101)
    - Saari - Samant, 1964-1974 (Box 101)
    - Samaras, Lucas, 1964-1984; 5 (Box 101)
    - Sandback - Sarkisian, 1966-1988 (Box 102)
    - Saura - Schwartz, 1964-1993 (Box 102)
    - Schwedler, William, 1972-1983 (Box 102)
    - Schwitters, Kurt, 1959-1990 (Box 102)
    - Scott, William, 1973-1990 (Box 102)
    - Scoville, Jonathan, 1986, 1987 (Box 102)
    - Sedgley, Edwina, 1969-1985 (Box 102)
    - Segal, George, 1960-1988; 2 (Box 102)
    - Sekiya, Yoshimichi, 1957 (Box 102)
    - Seliger, Chalres, 1959-1988 (Box 102)
    - Selina, Howard, 1973 (Box 102)
    - Shannon, Joe, 1971-1989 (Box 102)
    - Shapiro, Joel, 1963-1990 (Box 102)
    - Shaw, Jim - Shaw, Charles - Shaw, Richard, 1966-1994 (Box 102)
    - Shedletsky - Sherrod - Shields - Siemonowski, 1975-1991 (Box 102)
    - Silverman - Simonds - Singer - Sivalax, 1982-1994 (Box 102)
    - Smith, Cary, 1982-1994 (Box 103)
    - Smith, David, 1969-1994; 3 (Box 103)
    - Smith, Gregg, 1982-1984 (Box 103)
    - Smith, Richard, 1962-1991; 2 (Box 103)
    - Snelson, Kenneth, 1968-1981 (Box 103)
    - Soffer, Sasson, 1961-1966 (Box 103)
      Includes photograph of Soffer and Baker.
    - Sorel, Edward, 1973-1987 (Box 103)
    - Sorman, Steven, 1963-1991 (Box 103)
    - Soto, Jesus Rafael, 1965-1974 (Box 103)
    - Soulages, Pierre, 1956-1985 (Box 103)
    - Spira, Bill, 1984-1991 (Box 103)
    - Staiger, Paul, 1972,1981 (Box 103)
    - Stankiewicz, Richard, 1955-2002; 3 (Box 103)
    - Stephan, Gary, 1987-1994 (Box 103)
    - Steinberg, Saul, 1969-1988; 2 (Box 103)
    - Stella, Frank, 1963-1991; 5 (Box 104)
    - Stevenson, Harold, 1963-1977 (Box 104)
    - Stever, Jorge, 1974-1975 (Box 104)
    - Stollar, Lee, 1990 (Box 104)
    - Stotik, Eric, 1990-1997 (Box 104)
    - Stout, Myron, 1969-1991; 2 (Box 104)
    - Strunck, Juergen, 1967-1982 (Box 104)
    - Sugai, Kumi, 1959-1961 (Box 104)
    - Sugarman, George, 1961-1991 (Box 104)
    - Supplee, Sarah, 1984-1992 (Box 104)
    - Sutherland, Graham, 1973-1988 (Box 104)
    - Surls, James, 1957-1982 (Box 104)
    - Surmon, Angelita, 1985-1994 (Box 104)
    - Tadasky, 1965-1969 (Box 104)
    - Tajima, Hiroyuki, 1968, 1970 (Box 104)
    - Takamatsu, Jiro, 1968-1973 (Box 104)
    - Tansey, Mark, 1987-1990 (Box 104)
    - Tapies, Antoni, 1959-1992; 2 (Box 104)
    - Tarantal, Stephen, 1972-1981 (Box 105)
    - Taylor, Prentiss, 1969 (Box 105)
    - Teshigahara, Hiroshi, 1990 (Box 105)
    - Tetherow, Michael, 1990-1991 (Box 105)
    - Thepot - Tiemann - Tilson, 1960-1970 (Box 105)
    - Theibaud, Wayne, 1964-1988 (Box 105)
    - Tobey, Mark, 1969-1984 (Box 105)
    - Tornero - Torres, 1987-1990 (Box 105)
    - Tousignant - Trevanti, 1965-1989 (Box 105)
    - Tremleh, David, 1981-1984 (Box 105)
    - Trova, Ernest, 1967-1990; 2 (Box 105)
    - Tucker, William, 1977-1985 (Box 105)
    - Turner, J.M.W., 1958-1964 (Box 105)
    - Turcato - Turturro, 1956-1970 (Box 105)
    - Tuttle, Richard, 1968-1992; 2 (Box 105)
    - Tweddle, John, 1970-1976 (Box 105)
    - Twombly, Cy, 1969-1988; 2 (Box 105)
    - Tworkov, Jack, 1957-1984; 2 (Box 105)
    - Tyrell, Brinsley, 1983-1984 (Box 105)
    - Uhrig - Urry - Usui, 1958-1994 (Box 105)
    - Vaadia, Boaz, 1988-1992 (Box 105)
    - Valero, James, 1981-1994 (Box 106)
    - Van Dalen, Anton, 1984-1988 (Box 106)
    - Vanderburg, Albert, 1965-1976 (Box 106)
    - Vandercam, Serge, 1958 (Box 106)
    - Vasa, 1967-1975 (Box 106)
    - Vasarely, Victor, 1956-1987 (Box 106)
    - Vaughan, Keith, 1963-1966 (Box 106)
    - Vidal, Miguel Angel, 1983 (Box 106)
    - Vincente, Esteban, 1969-1992 (Box 106)
    - Viseux, Claude, 1957-1964 (Box 106)
    - Von Barann, Lawrence, 1992-1994 (Box 106)
    - Von Schlegell, David, 1965-1968 (Box 106)
    - Von Wicht - Vuksanovich, 1960-1994 (Box 106)
    - Wagemaker - Wakao, 1963-1966 (Box 106)
    - Walker, John, 1987-1993 (Box 106)
    - Wall, Brian, 1979-1983 (Box 106)
    - Wall, Sue, 1980-1994 (Box 106)
    - Wardy, Frederick, 1973-1980 (Box 106)
    - Pop Brochure, 1964, 1969 (Box 106)
    - Warhol, Andy, 1965-1994; 6 (Box 106)
    - Warrens, Robert, 1974-2000 (Box 106)
    - Weber, Idelle, 1979-1994 (Box 107)
    - Weiss - Weldon, 1979-1992 (Box 107)
    - Welliver, Neil, 1962-1981 (Box 107)
    - Werner, Theodore, 1955-1963 (Box 107)
    - Wesley, John, 1963-1980 (Box 107)
    - Wesselman, Tom, 1964-1990; 2 (Box 107)
    - Westermann, H.C., 1961-1990 (Box 107)
    - Wethli, Mark, 1974-1988 (Box 107)
    - Whistler, James MacNeil, 1953-1964 (Box 107)
    - Whiteley, Brett, 1991 (Box 107)
    - Whorf, John, 1956-1969 (Box 107)
    - Wiley, William, 1968-1990; 2 (Box 107)
    - Willenbecher, John, 1964-1979; 2 (Box 107)
      Includes 2 photographs of Willenbecher and Baker.
    - Williams, Danny, 1978-1984 (Box 107)
    - Wilson, May, 1967-1991 (Box 107)
    - Winter, Fritz, 1954-1983 (Box 107)
    - Witkin, Brian, 1969-1988 (Box 107)
    - Wood, Richard, undated (Box 107)
    - Woodburn, Stephen, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Wojciechowsky, A, 1963 (Box 107)
    - Wool, Christopher, 1988-1991; 3 (Box 107)
    - Yahura, Kazuo, 1967-1968 (Box 107)
    - Youngerman, Jack, 1986 (Box 107)